Guide to the Time Inc. Time Research Center Files: Subject Files MS 3009-RG 13.Series III
New-York Historical Society
- Series III. Subject Files, 1926-2000; 774 Linear feet (774 boxes)
  - Wars: Arab-Israeli: Reactions: K, 1970 (Offsite-box 2422, Folder 5)
  - Wars: Arab-Israeli: Reactions: L, 1967-1973 (Offsite-box 2422, Folder 6)
  - Wars: Arab-Israeli: Reactions: M, 1967-1979 (Offsite-box 2422, Folder 7)
  - Wars: Arab-Israeli: Reactions: N, 1967-1974 (Offsite-box 2422, Folder 8)
  - Wars: Arab-Israeli: Reactions: P, 1967-1972 (Offsite-box 2422, Folder 9)
  - Wars: Arab-Israeli: Reactions: R, 1967-1972 (Offsite-box 2422, Folder 10)
  - Wars: Arab-Israeli: Reactions: Religions, 1967-1982 (Offsite-box 2422, Folder 11)
  - Wars: Arab-Israeli: Reactions: S, 1967-1977 (Offsite-box 2422, Folder 12)
  - Wars: Arab-Israeli: Reactions: T, 1967-1969 (Offsite-box 2422, Folder 13)
  - Wars: Arab-Israeli: Reactions: U, 1967-1971 (Offsite-box 2422, Folder 14)
  - Wars: Arab-Israeli: Reactions: Union of Soviet Socialist Republics, 1967-1985 (Offsite-box 2422, Folder 15-18)
  - Wars: Arab-Israeli: Reactions: United Arab Republic, 1967-1975 (Offsite-box 2422, Folder 19-22)
  - Wars: Arab-Israeli: Reactions: United States, 1967-1989 (Offsite-box 2422, Folder 23-30)
  - Wars: Arab-Israeli: Reactions: United States: Associations, 1967-1972 (Offsite-box 2422, Folder 31)
  - Wars: Arab-Israeli: Reactions: United States: Education, 1967-1970 (Offsite-box 2422, Folder 32)
  - Wars: Arab-Israeli: Reactions: United States: Government, 1967-1972 (Offsite-box 2422, Folder 33)
  - Wars: Arab-Israeli: Reactions: United States: Government: Congress, 1967 (Offsite-box 2423, Folder 1)
  - Wars: Arab-Israeli: Reactions: "Negro" [African American], 1967-1972 (Offsite-box 2423, Folder 2)
  - Wars: Arab-Israeli: Reactions: Polls, 1967-1970 (Offsite-box 2423, Folder 3)
  - Wars: Arab-Israeli: Reactions: Polls, 1967-1970 (Offsite-box 2423, Folder 4)
  - Wars: Arab-Israeli: Reactions: V, 1967 (Offsite-box 2423, Folder 5)
  - Wars: Arab-Israeli: Reactions: Y, 1967-1972 (Offsite-box 2423, Folder 6)
  - Wars: Arab-Israeli: Records, 1967-1973 (Offsite-box 2423, Folder 7)
  - Wars: Arab-Israeli: Reperations, 1967-1972 (Offsite-box 2423, Folder 8)
  - Wars: Arab-Israeli: Strategy, 1967-1972 (Offsite-box 2423, Folder 9-13)
  - Wars: Arab-Israeli: Surveys, 1966-1992 (Offsite-box 2423, Folder 14-16)
  - Wars: Arab-Israeli: Tactics, 1967-1973 (Offsite-box 2423, Folder 17)
  - Wars: Arab-Israeli: Truces, 1967-1976 (Offsite-box 2423, Folder 18-25)
  - Wars: Arab-Israeli: Truces: Violations, 1971-1973 (Offsite-box 2423, Folder 26-30)
  - Wars: Arab-Israeli: Truces: Violations, 1967-1971 (Offsite-box 2424, Folder 1-12)
  - Wars: Arab-Israeli: Works about, 1987-1989 (Offsite-box 2424, Folder 13)
  - Wars: Korea, 1952-1993 (Offsite-box 2424, Folder 14-20)
  - Wars: Korea, 1951-1952 (Offsite-box 2425, Folder 1-15)
  - Wars: Korea, 1950-1951 (Offsite-box 2426, Folder 1-13)
  - Wars: Korea, 1950 (Offsite-box 2427, Folder 1)
  - Wars: Korea: Atrocities, 1950-1955 (Offsite-box 2427, Folder 2-6)
  - Wars: Korea: Biological warfare, 1952-1954 (Offsite-box 2427, Folder 7-12)
  - Wars: Korea: Biological warfare: Bacterial warfare, 1951-1952 (Offsite-box 2427, Folder 13-14)
  - Wars: Korea: Casualities, 1952-1993 (Offsite-box 2427, Folder 15-17)
  - Wars: Korea: Casualities, 1950-1951 (Offsite-box 2428, Folder 1-4)
  - Wars: Korea: Chemical warfare, 1952-1953 (Offsite-box 2428, Folder 5)
  - Wars: Korea: Costs, 1951-1973 (Offsite-box 2428, Folder 6)
  - Wars: Korea: Losses, 1950-1990 (Offsite-box 2428, Folder 7-8)
  - Wars: Korea: Memorials, 1989-1992 (Offsite-box 2428, Folder 9)
  - Wars: Korea: Memorials: Associations, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 2428, Folder 10)
  - Wars: Korea: News coverage, 1950-1992 (Offsite-box 2428, Folder 11-12)
  - Wars: Korea: Peace plans, 1954-1993 (Offsite-box 2428, Folder 13-24)
  - Wars: Korea: Peace plans, 1952-1953 (Offsite-box 2429, Folder 1-14)
  - Wars: Korea: Peace plans, 1950-1951 (Offsite-box 2430, Folder 1-9)
  - Wars: Korea: Prisoners, 1952-1993 (Offsite-box 2430, Folder 10-19)
  - Wars: Korea: Prisoners, 1950-1952 (Offsite-box 2431, Folder 1-10)
  - Wars: Korea: Prisoners: Australia, 1953 (Offsite-box 2431, Folder 11)
  - Wars: Korea: Prisoners: China, Communist and Korea, Northern, 1953-1987 (Offsite-box 2431, Folder 12-15)
  - Wars: Korea: Prisoners: Colombia, 1953-1954 (Offsite-box 2431, Folder 16)
  - Wars: Korea: Prisoners: Exchanges, 1953-1959 (Offsite-box 2431, Folder 17-23)
  - Wars: Korea: Prisoners: France, 1956 (Offsite-box 2431, Folder 24)
  - Wars: Korea: Prisoners: Great Britain, 1953-1960 (Offsite-box 2431, Folder 25)
  - Wars: Korea: Prisoners: Korea, Southern, 1953-1958 (Offsite-box 2431, Folder 26)
  - Wars: Korea: Prisoners: Morocco, 1955-1965 (Offsite-box 2431, Folder 27)
  - Wars: Korea: Prisoners: Repatriation refusers, 1954-1961 (Offsite-box 2431, Folder 28)
  - Wars: Korea: Prisoners: Repatriation refusers, 1953-1954 (Offsite-box 2432, Folder 1-11)
  - Wars: Korea: Prisoners: Repatriation refusers: Belgium, 1955 (Offsite-box 2432, Folder 12)
  - Wars: Korea: Prisoners: Repatriation refusers: Great Britain, 1954-1956 (Offsite-box 2432, Folder 13)
  - Wars: Korea: Prisoners: Repatriation refusers: Korea, Southern, 1953-1954 (Offsite-box 2432, Folder 14)
  - Wars: Korea: Prisoners: Repatriation refusers: United Nations, 1953-1954 (Offsite-box 2432, Folder 15)
  - Wars: Korea: Prisoners: Repatriation refusers: United States, 1953-1963 (Offsite-box 2432, Folder 16-17)
  - Wars: Korea: Prisoners: South Africa, 1953 (Offsite-box 2432, Folder 18)
  - Wars: Korea: Prisoners: Turkey, 1955 (Offsite-box 2432, Folder 19)
  - Wars: Korea: Prisoners: Union of the Soviet Socialist Republics, 1961 (Offsite-box 2432, Folder 20)
  - Wars: Korea: Prisoners: United Nations, 1953-1965 (Offsite-box 2432, Folder 21-24)
  - Wars: Korea: Prisoners: United States, 1953-1991 (Offsite-box 2432, Folder 25-28)
  - Wars: Korea: Prisoners: United States: Associations, 1954 (Offsite-box 2432, Folder 29)
  - Wars: Korea: Prisoners: United States: Collaboration, treatment, etc., 1953-1993 (Offsite-box 2433, Folder 1-3)
  - Wars: Korea: Publications, 1988-1992 (Offsite-box 2433, Folder 4)
  - Wars: Korea: Reactions, 1950-1954 (Offsite-box 2433, Folder 5)
  - Wars: Korea: Reactions: A-Z, 1950-1953 (Offsite-box 2433, Folder 6-10)
  - Wars: Korea: Reactions: Argentina, 1950 (Offsite-box 2433, Folder 11)
  - Wars: Korea: Reactions: China, 1950-1992 (Offsite-box 2433, Folder 12)
  - Wars: Korea: Reactions: East, Far, 1950-1953 (Offsite-box 2433, Folder 13)
  - Wars: Korea: Reactions: Europe, 1950 (Offsite-box 2433, Folder 14)
  - Wars: Korea: Reactions: France, 1950-1952 (Offsite-box 2433, Folder 15)
  - Wars: Korea: Reactions: Germany, 1950 (Offsite-box 2433, Folder 16)
  - Wars: Korea: Reactions: Great Britain, 1950-1954 (Offsite-box 2433, Folder 17)
  - Wars: Korea: Reactions: India, 1950-1954 (Offsite-box 2433, Folder 18)
  - Wars: Korea: Reactions: Italy, 1950 (Offsite-box 2433, Folder 19)
  - Wars: Korea: Reactions: Japan, 1951 (Offsite-box 2433, Folder 20)
  - Wars: Korea: Reactions: Korea, 1950-1992 (Offsite-box 2433, Folder 21-22)
  - Wars: Korea: Reactions: Philippines, 1950 (Offsite-box 2433, Folder 23)
  - Wars: Korea: Reactions: Union of Soviet Socialist Republics, 1950-1953 (Offsite-box 2433, Folder 24)
  - Wars: Korea: Reactions: United States, 1950-1990 (Offsite-box 2433, Folder 25-29)
  - Wars: Korea: Reactions: Yugoslavia, 1950-1951 (Offsite-box 2433, Folder 30)
  - Wars: Korea: Reperations, 1952-1990 (Offsite-box 2433, Folder 31)
  - Wars: Korea: Strategy, 1953-1992 (Offsite-box 2433, Folder 32-33)
  - Wars: Korea: Termination, 1988 (Offsite-box 2485, Folder 1)
  - Wars: Korea: Eighth Parallel Crossing Question, 1951 (Offsite-box 2485, Folder 2)
  - Wars: Korea: War criminals, 1950-1955 (Offsite-box 2485, Folder 3)
  - Wars: Korea: Works about, 1983-1991 (Offsite-box 2485, Folder 4)
  - Wars: Lebanon, 1982-1993 (Offsite-box 2485, Folder 5-16)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Air operations, 1982-1985 (Offsite-box 2485, Folder 17)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Atrocities, 1982-1984 (Offsite-box 2485, Folder 18)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Casualties, 1982-1992 (Offsite-box 2485, Folder 19-26)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Chronology, 1982-1984 (Offsite-box 2485, Folder 27)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Comparisons with other wars, 1983-1990 (Offsite-box 2485, Folder 28)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Costs, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 2485, Folder 29)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Economic aspects, 1982-1984 (Offsite-box 2485, Folder 30)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Effects, 1983-1985 (Offsite-box 2485, Folder 31-32)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Effects, 1982 (Offsite-box 2486, Folder 1)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Foreign armed forces, 1982-1984 (Offsite-box 2486, Folder 2)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Investigations, 1983 (Offsite-box 2486, Folder 3)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Losses, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 2486, Folder 4)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Moral aspects, 1983 (Offsite-box 2486, Folder 5)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Naval operations, 1982-1984 (Offsite-box 2486, Folder 6)
  - Wars: Lebanon: News coverage, 1982-1985 (Offsite-box 2486, Folder 7-9)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Peace plans, 1983-1987 (Offsite-box 2486, Folder 10-23)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Peace plans, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 2487, Folder 1-12)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Postwar aspects, 1982-1985 (Offsite-box 2487, Folder 13-15)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Prisoners, 1982-1985 (Offsite-box 2487, Folder 16)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Publications, 1984-1990 (Offsite-box 2487, Folder 17)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Reactions, 1982-1984 (Offsite-box 2487, Folder 18)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Reactions: East, Near, 1982-1984 (Offsite-box 2487, Folder 19)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Reactions: Egypt, 1982-1985 (Offsite-box 2487, Folder 20)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Reactions: Egypt: Associations, 1982 (Offsite-box 2487, Folder 21)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Reactions: France, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 2487, Folder 22)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Reactions: International, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 2487, Folder 23)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Reactions: Israel, 1984-1989 (Offsite-box 2487, Folder 24)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Reactions: Israel, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 2488, Folder 1-3)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Reactions: Israel: Associations, 1982 (Offsite-box 2488, Folder 4)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Reactions: Jordan, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 2488, Folder 5)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Reactions: Lebanon, 1982-1985 (Offsite-box 2488, Folder 6)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Reactions: Palestine, 1982-1984 (Offsite-box 2488, Folder 7)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Reactions: Religious, 1982-1984 (Offsite-box 2488, Folder 8)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Reactions: Saudi Arabia, 1982-1984 (Offsite-box 2488, Folder 9)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Reactions: Syria, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 2488, Folder 10)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Reactions: Union of Soviet Socialist Republics, 1982-1984 (Offsite-box 2488, Folder 11)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Reactions: United Nations, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 2488, Folder 12)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Reactions: United States, 1982-1993 (Offsite-box 2488, Folder 13)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Reactions: United States: Associations, 1982 (Offsite-box 2488, Folder 14)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Reactions: United States: Associations: Concerned Americans for Peace, 1982 (Offsite-box 2488, Folder 15)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Reactions: United States: Demonstrations, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 2488, Folder 16)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Reactions: United States: Government, 1982-1985 (Offsite-box 2488, Folder 17-21)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Reactions: United States: Government: Congress, 1982-1984 (Offsite-box 2488, Folder 22)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Reactions: United States: Jews, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 2488, Folder 23)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Reactions: United States: Polls, 1982-1984 (Offsite-box 2488, Folder 24)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Reactions: United States: Press, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 2488, Folder 25)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Records (Superlatives), 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 2489, Folder 1)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Relief, 1982-1986 (Offsite-box 2489, Folder 2)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Relief: United States, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 2489, Folder 3)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Relief: United States: Associations: American Corporate Aid for Lebanon, 1982 (Offsite-box 2489, Folder 4)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Reparations, 1984 (Offsite-box 2489, Folder 5)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Strategy, 1982-1990 (Offsite-box 2489, Folder 6)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Surveys, 1982-1985 (Offsite-box 2489, Folder 7)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Tactics, 1982-1984 (Offsite-box 2489, Folder 8-10)
  - Wars: Lebanon: Truces, 1982-1984 (Offsite-box 2489, Folder 11)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf, 1990-1993 (Offsite-box 2489, Folder 12-22)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf, 1990 (Offsite-box 2490, Folder 1-11)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Air operations, 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 2490, Folder 12-16)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Air operations, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 2491, Folder 1-8)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Amphibious operations, 1991 (Offsite-box 2491, Folder 9)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Atomic warfare, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 2491, Folder 10)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Atrocities, 1990-1992 (Offsite-box 2491, Folder 11-12)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Attacks on allied and own forces, 1990-1992 (Offsite-box 2491, Folder 13)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Biological and chemical warfare, 1991 (Offsite-box 2491, Folder 14)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Biological and chemical warfare, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 2492, Folder 1-5)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Blockade zone, 1990 (Offsite-box 2492, Folder 6)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Booty, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 2492, Folder 7)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Casualties, 1990-1993 (Offsite-box 2492, Folder 8-11)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Casualties: A-Z, 1990-1992 (Offsite-box 2492, Folder 12)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Casualties: Iraq, 1991 (Offsite-box 2492, Folder 13-14)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Casualties: United States, 1991-1993 (Offsite-box 2492, Folder 15-22)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Casualties: United States, 1990 (Offsite-box 2493, Folder 1)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Chronology, 1990-1993 (Offsite-box 2493, Folder 2-4)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Comparison with other wars, 1990-1992 (Offsite-box 2493, Folder 5-8)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Costs, 1990-1992 (Offsite-box 2493, Folder 9-18)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Duration, 1991 (Offsite-box 2493, Folder 19)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Economic aspects, 1991-1993 (Offsite-box 2493, Folder 20-24)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Economic aspects, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 2494, Folder 1-12)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Economic aspects, 1990 (Offsite-box 2495, Folder 1)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Effects, 1990-1993 (Offsite-box 2495, Folder 2-10)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: History, 1991-1993 (Offsite-box 2495, Folder 11)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Losses, 1990-1992 (Offsite-box 2495, Folder 12-17)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Memorials, 1991 (Offsite-box 2495, Folder 18)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Merchandising, 1991 (Offsite-box 2495, Folder 19)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Moral aspects, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 2495, Folder 20)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Naval operations, 1990-1993 (Offsite-box 2496, Folder 1)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: News coverage, 1990-1993 (Offsite-box 2496, Folder 2-12)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Peace plans, 1992-1993 (Offsite-box 2496, Folder 13-14)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Peace plans, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 2497, Folder 1-13)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Peace plans: Violations, 1993 (Offsite-box 2497, Folder 14)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Peace plans: Violations, 1993 (Offsite-box 2498, Folder 1)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Polls, 1990-1993 (Offsite-box 2498, Folder 2-9)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Post-war aspects, 1991-1993 (Offsite-box 2498, Folder 10-20)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Post-war aspects, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 2499, Folder 1-2)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Prisoners, 1990-1993 (Offsite-box 2499, Folder 3-10)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Prisoners: Repatriation refusers, 1991-1993 (Offsite-box 2499, Folder 11)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Publications, 1991-1993 (Offsite-box 2499, Folder 12)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Reactions: A-Z, 1990-1993 (Offsite-box 2499, Folder 13-17)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Reactions: Africa, 1991 (Offsite-box 2499, Folder 18)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Reactions: Australia, 1990-1992 (Offsite-box 2500, Folder 1)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Reactions: Bangladesh, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 2500, Folder 2)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Reactions: Canada, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 2500, Folder 3)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Reactions: China, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 2500, Folder 4)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Reactions: East, Far, 1990 (Offsite-box 2500, Folder 5)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Reactions: East, Near, 1990-1993 (Offsite-box 2500, Folder 6-10)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Reactions: Egypt, 1990-1992 (Offsite-box 2500, Folder 11-15)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Reactions: Europe, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 2500, Folder 16)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Reactions: France, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 2500, Folder 17-20)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Reactions: Germany, 1990-1992 (Offsite-box 2501, Folder 1-4)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Reactions: Great Britain, 1990-1992 (Offsite-box 2501, Folder 5-8)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Reactions: Great Britain: Associations, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 2501, Folder 9)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Reactions: International, 1990-1993 (Offsite-box 2501, Folder 10-17)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Reactions: Iran, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 2501, Folder 18)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Reactions: Iraq, 1991-1993 (Offsite-box 2501, Folder 19-24)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Reactions: Iraq, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 2502, Folder 1-5)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Reactions: Israel, 1990-1993 (Offsite-box 2502, Folder 6-14)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Reactions: Italy, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 2502, Folder 15)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Reactions: Japan, 1990-1992 (Offsite-box 2502, Folder 16-18)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Reactions: Jordan, 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 2502, Folder 19-22)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Reactions: Jordan, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 2503, Folder 1-3)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Reactions: Kuwait, 1990-1992 (Offsite-box 2503, Folder 4-5)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Reactions: Kuwait: Associations, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 2503, Folder 6)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Reactions: Libya, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 2503, Folder 7)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Reactions: Morocco, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 2503, Folder 8)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Reactions: North Atlantic Treaty Organization, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 2503, Folder 9)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Reactions: Pakistan, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 2503, Folder 10)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Reactions: Palestine, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 2503, Folder 11)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Reactions: Religious, 1990-1992 (Offsite-box 2503, Folder 12-18)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Reactions: Saudi Arabia, 1990-1993 (Offsite-box 2503, Folder 19-21)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Reactions: Saudi Arabia: Associations, 1990 (Offsite-box 2503, Folder 22)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Reactions: Syria, 1990-1993 (Offsite-box 2504, Folder 1)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Reactions: Tunisia, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 2504, Folder 2)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Reactions: Turkey, 1990-1993 (Offsite-box 2504, Folder 3-5)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Reactions: Union of Soviet Socialist Republics, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 2504, Folder 6-10)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Reactions: United States, 1991-1993 (Offsite-box 2504, Folder 11-20)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Reactions: United States, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 2505, Folder 1-14)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Reactions: United States, 1990 (Offsite-box 2518, Folder 1)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Reactions: United States: Associations, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 2518, Folder 2)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Reactions: United States: Demonstrations, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 2518, Folder 3-4)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Reactions: United States: Government, 1990-1992 (Offsite-box 2518, Folder 5-16)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Reactions: United States: Government, 1990 (Offsite-box 2519, Folder 1-5)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Reactions: Yemen, 1990 (Offsite-box 2519, Folder 6)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Reperations, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 2519, Folder 7)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Strategy, 1991-1993 (Offsite-box 2519, Folder 8-20)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Strategy, 1990 (Offsite-box 2520, Folder 1-4)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Surveys, 1990-1992 (Offsite-box 2520, Folder 5-11)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Tactics, 1991-1993 (Offsite-box 2520, Folder 12-17)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Tactics, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 2521, Folder 1-4)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Termination, 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 2521, Folder 5)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Terminology, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 2521, Folder 6)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: War criminals, 1990-1993 (Offsite-box 2521, Folder 7)
  - Wars: Persian Gulf: Works about, 1991-1993 (Offsite-box 2521, Folder 8)
  - Wars: Vietnam, 1969-1993 (Offsite-box 2521, Folder 9-20)
  - Wars: Vietnam, 1967-1969 (Offsite-box 2522)
  - Wars: Vietnam, 1966-1967 (Offsite-box 2523, Folder 1-15)
  - Wars: Vietnam, 1965-1966 (Offsite-box 2524, Folder 1-17)
  - Wars: Vietnam, 1965 (Offsite-box 2525, Folder 1-15)
  - Wars: Vietnam, 1964-1965 (Offsite-box 2526, Folder 1-14)
  - Wars: Vietnam: Air operations, 1972-1991 (Offsite-box 2526, Folder 15-28)
  - Wars: Vietnam: Air operations, 1970-1972 (Offsite-box 2527, Folder 1-15)
  - Wars: Vietnam: Air operations, 1967-1969 (Offsite-box 2528, Folder 1-14)
  - Wars: Vietnam: Air operations, 1966-1967 (Offsite-box 2529, Folder 1-14)
  - Wars: Vietnam: Air operations, 1965-1966 (Offsite-box 2530, Folder 1-12)
  - Wars: Vietnam: Air operations, 1965 (Offsite-box 2531, Folder 1-7)
  - Wars: Vietnam: Air operations: Cambodia, 1964-1987 (Offsite-box 2531, Folder 8-19)
  - Wars: Vietnam: Air operations: Laos, 1974 (Offsite-box 2531, Folder 20)
  - Wars: Vietnam: Air operations: Laos, 1965-1973 (Offsite-box 2532, Folder 1-9)
  - Wars: Vietnam: Air operations: Thailand, 1967-1969 (Offsite-box 2532, Folder 10)
  - Wars: Vietnam: Amphibious operations, 1966-1984 (Offsite-box 2532, Folder 11-14)
  - Wars: Vietnam: Atomic warfare, 1964-1971 (Offsite-box 2532, Folder 15)
  - Wars: Vietnam: Atrocities, 1965-1985 (Offsite-box 2532, Folder 16-24)
  - Wars: Vietnam: Atrocities: My Lai 4, 1971-1992 (Offsite-box 2532, Folder 25-30)
  - Wars: Vietnam: Atrocities: My Lai 4, 1969-1971 (Offsite-box 2533, Folder 1-10)
  - Wars: Vietnam: Attacks on allied and own forces, 1964-1975 (Offsite-box 2533, Folder 11-13)
  - Wars: Vietnam: Biological warfare, 1968 (Offsite-box 2533, Folder 14)
  - Wars: Vietnam: Booty, 1972-1981 (Offsite-box 2533, Folder 15)
  - Wars: Vietnam: Cambodia, Operations in, 1972-1988 (Offsite-box 2533, Folder 16-22)
  - Wars: Vietnam: Cambodia, Operations in, 1966-1971 (Offsite-box 2534, Folder 1-7)
  - Wars: Vietnam: Casualties, 1968-1993 (Offsite-box 2534, Folder 8-14)
  - Wars: Vietnam: Casualties: A-Z, 1975-1985 (Offsite-box 2534, Folder 15)
  - Wars: Vietnam: Casualties: Australia, 1966-1987 (Offsite-box 2534, Folder 16)
  - Wars: Vietnam: Casualties: Cambodia, 1970-1990 (Offsite-box 2534, Folder 17)
  - Wars: Vietnam: Casualties: China, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 2534, Folder 18)
  - Wars: Vietnam: Casualties: International, 1965-1972 (Offsite-box 2534, Folder 19-22)
  - Wars: Vietnam: Casualties: Korea, 1970-1992 (Offsite-box 2534, Folder 23)
  - Wars: Vietnam: Casualties: Laos, 1968-1992 (Offsite-box 2534, Folder 24)
  - Wars: Vietnam: Casualties: New Zealand, 1965-1968 (Offsite-box 2534, Folder 25)
  - Wars: Vietnam: Casualties: Thailand, 1969 (Offsite-box 2534, Folder 26)
  - Wars: Vietnam: Casualties: United States, 1985-1993 (Offsite-box 2534, Folder 27-30)
  - Wars: Vietnam: Casualties: United States, 1965-1984 (Offsite-box 2535, Folder 1-32)
  - Wars: Vietnam: Casualties: United States, 1964 (Offsite-box 2536, Folder 1)
  - Wars: Vietnam: Casualties: United States: Bodies, 1968-1993 (Offsite-box 2536, Folder 2-6)
  - Wars: Vietnam: Casualties: United States: Civilians, 1968-1985 (Offsite-box 2536, Folder 7)
  - Wars: Vietnam: Casualties: United States: Reports, 1968-1993 (Offsite-box 2536, Folder 8)
  - Wars: Vietnam: Casualties: Vietnam, 1964-1993 (Offsite-box 2536, Folder 9-22)